<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<odoo>

   <template id="aboutus">
        <div class="oe_structure home-page-cover">
            <section
                class="s_text_block_image_fw oe_img_bg oe_custom_bg text-center background-header-typ"
                style="background-image: url(/web/image/theme_typ.hero-about);"
            >
                <div class="container">
                    <div class="row">
                        <h1 class="header-titles hidden-xs">WHO WE ARE IN T&amp;P<br
                            />REFRIGERATION</h1>
                        <h1
                            class="header-titles mr16 ml16 hidden-lg hidden-sm hidden-md"
                        >WHO WE ARE IN T&amp;P<br />REFRIGERATION</h1>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </section>
        </div>
        <div class="oe_structure oe_empty dark-white">
            <div class="container general-typ-information">
                <div
                    class="col-xs-12 col-sm-10 col-sm-offset-1 col-xs-offset-0 mt32 mb96"
                >
                    <div class="menu-options">
                        <ul class="nav nav-tabs">
                            <li class="active"><a
                                    data-toggle="tab"
                                    href="#about"
                                >About us</a></li>
                            <li><a
                                    data-toggle="tab"
                                    href="#mision"
                                >Mision, vision and values</a></li>
                            <li><a
                                    data-toggle="tab"
                                    href="#policies"
                                >Sale Policies</a></li>
                        </ul>
                    </div>
                    <div class="tab-content">
                        <div id="about" class="tab-pane fade in active">
                            <p class="typ-text">
                                In <strong
                                >T&amp;P Refrigeration</strong> we are a wholesale commercial company with more than 20 years of experience,
                                with its operations center in Hermosillo, Sonora, Mexico. We have six points of sale located in the Northwest of Mexico,
                                in the States of Sonora, Sinaloa and Baja California and also in the Operations and Distribution Center located in the
                                city of Hermosillo, Sonora.
                            </p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                We are dedicated to the commercialization of spare parts, installation materials and equipment for air conditioning,
                                refrigeration and air ventilation, being our primary objective to serve the contractors of these branches, both in the Northwest
                                of Mexico through our establishments and through of our new store option by phone and internet to serve the rest of the country.
                            </p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                We are distributors of important manufacturers of the products we sell, both in Mexico and the United States, which allows us to
                                provide a wide range of alternatives for market needs, technical support, guarantees and trained personnel to support investments
                                of those who use our services.
                            </p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                As of 2006, we are active members of HARDI, an organization that groups more than 450 distribution companies and more than 300
                                associated manufacturing companies, mainly in the United States, and that represent little more than 80% of the value of products
                                sold through distribution companies. .
                            </p>
                            <p class="title mt32">Background</p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                T&amp;P Refrigeracion is a regional company specialized in the attention to contractor companies, which operates in the Northwest
                                of the Mexican Republic. Established more than 20 years ago, it has as its base of operations the city of
                                Hermosillo, Sonora, Mexico, and is dedicated to the commercialization of equipment, installation materials and refurbishments
                                for Air Conditioning, Refrigeration and Ventilation.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div id="mision" class="tab-pane fade">
                            <p class="title">
                                Mision
                            </p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                To effectively satisfy the supply of products and services to our customers, generating mutual business opportunities,
                                backed by our values, innovation and development of our collaborators.
                            </p>
                            <p class="title mt32">
                                Vision
                            </p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                To be a leading company in the marketing of air conditioning and refrigeration products in the northwest and with presence in other territories
                                of the Mexican Republic operating as an intelligent company.
                            </p>
                            <p class="title mt32">
                                Values
                            </p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                Unquestionable values:
                                <ul>
                                    <li>Commitment.</li>
                                    <li>Honesty.</li>
                                    <li>Loyalty.</li>
                                    <li>Respect.</li>
                                    <li>Responsibility</li>
                                </ul>
                            </p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                Desirable values:
                                <ul>
                                    <li>Humility.</li>
                                    <li>Continuous improvement.</li>
                                    <li>Passion for the service.</li>
                                    <li>Proactivity</li>
                                    <li>Social responsability.</li>
                                    <li>Teamwork.</li>
                                </ul>
                            </p>
                            <h5
                                class="sections mt48 text-center"
                            >WE SUPPORT THE SUCCESS OF YOUR BUSINESS</h5>
                        </div>
                        <div id="policies" class="tab-pane fade">
                            <p class="title">
                                Contracting companies
                            </p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                <p class="subtitle mb0">Minimum Purchases:</p>
                                <p>
                                    There is no minimum purchase limit. Any number of products, regardless of their price will be attended.
                                </p>
                            </p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                <p class="subtitle mb0">Prices:</p>
                                <p>
                                    Purchase orders will be invoiced at current prices on the date of shipment.
                                    All prices are subject to change without notice as long as they are not billed.
                                </p>
                            </p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                <p class="subtitle mb0">Payment Methods:</p>
                                <p>
                                   Purchase orders will be filled upon receipt of the total payment of the products or it is suggested to make the payments
                                   preferably using the electronic banking system, for the agile and secure of this type of transactions.
                                </p>
                            </p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                <p class="subtitle mb0">Credit:</p>
                                <p>
                                   Available to customers with an authorized and current line of credit. Credit sales invoices will cause interest if they are not paid when due.
                                   Purchase orders from customers with suspended credit will not be processed.
                                </p>
                            </p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                <p class="subtitle mb0">Returns:</p>
                                <p>
                                   Any return of products arising from causes attributable to the buyer, will generate a charge of 20% on the value of your shipment, will be freight
                                   paid by the customer to the branch that corresponds. If the products are returned for reasons attributable to T&amp;P Refrigeración or to the manufacturers
                                   of the product, the money will be returned or a credit will be extended to the customer's account after receiving and having accepted the return.
                                </p>
                            </p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                <p class="subtitle mb0">Freight:</p>
                                <p>
                                  All prices are L.A.B. point of sale or assortment of T&amp;P Refrigeration. The freight charges for shipping products are charged to the customer,
                                  who will pay them when they are received. In case of receiving damaged or missing products, the customer must immediately claim the freight company.
                                </p>
                            </p>
                            <p class="mt16">
                                <p class="subtitle mb0">Warranty:</p>
                                <p>
                                  All our products are guaranteed, however, the terms vary according to the policies and conditions established by each supplier or manufacturer.
                                  The electrical parts have no guarantee.
                                </p>
                            </p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
        <div class="oe_structure" />
   </template>

</odoo>
